Preliminary Guide to the Luther Brady papers, MS2147.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- UP0019 (Box 19)
  - PA Blue Shield Medical Affairs Committee Mtg., 6/8/94, Camp Hill, PA, 06/08/1994 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - PBS Philadelphia Regional Meeting, 6/2/94, Wyndham Franklin Plaza Hotel, 06/02/1994 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- UP0020 (Box 20)
  - New York University Med. Ctr., 2/16/96 - Residency Review (Jay Cooper, MD), 02/16/1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - ACS/Phila. Div. Capital Campaign Individuals' Gift Committee Mtg., 2/8/96, 1626 Locust St., Phila., 02/08/1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - CIM Audit Committee Mtg., 1/25/96, 1:30 pm, Bok Room, 01/25/1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - ACS Medical Affairs Advisory Group on Clinical Awards, Atlanta, GA, 1/4-5/96, 01/04/1996 - 01/05/1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Samuel S. Fleisher Art Memorial Development Committee Mtg., 1/22/96, 12 noon, Union League, 01/22/1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - ECOG Sit Mtg., Allegheny Gen. Hospital, Pittsburgh, PA, 1/15/96 (Dr. Mark Levitt), 01/15/1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Lehigh University, Bethlehem, PA, 12/28/95, 1 pm (Dr. Peter Likins, Ms. Jill Sherman, Ms. Marcia Theodoredis), Alumni Memorial Bldg, 12/28/1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - NYC - 12/1 & 2/95, 12/01/1995 - 12/02/1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Curtis Institute of Music--Major Gifts Committee Luncheon Mtg., Bok Rm., 12/1/95, 12 Noon, 12/01/1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Albert R. Taxin Brain Tumor Symposium, Wistar Institue, 11/30/95, 9am-6pm (Heidi L. Boorstein), 11/30/1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - PBS Special Members Mtg., 11/28/95, Hershey Lodge/Convention Ctr., Nigerian Rm., regretted, 11/28/1995 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - RSNA 81st Annual Mtg., 11/26-12/1/95, McCormick Place, Chicago, IL, 11/26/1995 - 12/01/1995 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - WWDB Radio, 11/15/95, 7:30 pm, Joel Posner, MD--Rad Onc: Advances in Cancer Treatment., 11/15/1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - ACS Annual Awards Celebration for Volunteers, 11/2/95, Adam's Mark Hotel, 11/02/1995 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Gynecologic Onc. Conference, 10/27/95, Lehigh Valley Hosp., Scranton, PA (Dr. Gazi Abdulhay, Chief), 10/27/1995 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - IAMA Board Meeting, 19th Fl. Board Rm., NCB, 10/14/95, 10/14/1995 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - "Diag. & Trtmt of Lung Cancer" Seminar, 10/11/95, 8:30 a - 3:30 p -- Dr. B's bet., 9:30 a & 12 n (15-20 min.), Alumni Hall, 10/11/1995 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - ASTRO Annual Mtg., Miami Beach Convention Ctr., Miami Beach, FL, 10/9-13/95, 10/09/1995 - 10/13/1995 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - BCRI: Scientific Symposium Bull., Four Seasons, 10/7/95, 10/07/1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Medical Conference Series: "Controversies in Breast Cancer Management, 10/5/95, 12 N, Main Mtg. Rm, Elkins Park Hosp., 10/05/1995 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Med. Conf. Series: "Breast Cancer Management"-Bucks Cty. Hospital, 9/27/95, 12 N, Main Mtg. Rm., Warminster, PA, 09/27/1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - HU Medical Staff Fall Mtg., Four Seasons, 9/19/95, in the Ballroom, 6 p.m. (George Amrom, MD, Pres., HU Med. Staff), 09/19/1995 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - RAMAS & L.W. BRADY, MD & ASSOC. Mtg., 9/16-17/95, Four Seasons, 09/16/1995 - 09/17/1995 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - PBS Medical Affairs Committee Mtg., 9/13/95, 9 a.m., Camp Hill, PA regretted, 09/13/1995 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Curtis Institute of Music Tea/Mtg., 9/13/95, 3:00 pm/3:30 pm, Rittenhouse Hotel, 210 W. Rittenhouse Sq, 19th Fl., 09/13/1995 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - ACS Capital Campaign Steering Com. Mtg. 9/13/95, 4 p.m., 1626 Locust St., Phila., PA (Johnathan M. Polisar), 09/13/1995 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - ACR Annual Mtg., Westin Hotel Copley Pl., 9/9-13/95, Boston, MA, 09/09/1995 - 09/13/1995 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - London, England & Brussels, Belgium, 8/30-9/5/95, 08/30/1995 - 09/05/1995 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - PBS Mtg.-Phila. Marriot West, West Conshohocken, PA, 8/17/95, 6:30 pm (re merger), 08/17/1995 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Santa Fe, New Mexico, 7/29-8/12/95, 07/29/1995 - 08/12/1995 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - GOG Semi-Annual Business Mtg., 7/21-23/95, Omni Hotel, Charleston, SC (Dr. Rober Park)--25th Anniversary, 07/21/1995 - 07/23/1995 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Paris, France - Chateaux de la Bretesche, 7/8-14/95 (Z. Petrovich, M.D.), 07/08/1995 - 07/14/1995 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - The Philip Rubin Symposium, 6/23-25/95, Rochester, NY, 06/23/1995 - 06/25/1995 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- UP0021 (Box 21)
  - IAMA Board Mtg., NYC, 3/28/97, 12 N, 03/28/1997 (Binder 21, Folder 1)
  - NCI Site Visit, DoubleTree Hotel, 3/24-25/97, Rockville, MD, 03/24/1997 - 03/25/1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Macular Degeneration Symposium, 3/21/97, Manhattan Sheraton Hotel (Anthony M. Berson, MD), 03/21/1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - PBS Medical Affairs Committee Mtg., 3/12/97 Camp Hill, PA (Ed. Resnick, MD, Chair) canceled, 03/12/1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Oncovail, Manor Vail Lodge, 3/2-7/97, Vail, CO, 03/02/1997 - 03/07/1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - DuPont Merck Radiopharmaceuticals, Billerica, MA, 2/26/97 (Richard A. Holmes, MD), 02/26/1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - MD/PhD Program, 2/19/96, 4:30-6:30 pm, Main Speaker: LWB (basic research to clinic)--John Langell, Coordinator, 02/19/1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - David Rotman, Palm Beach, FL, 2/7-9/97, 02/07/1997 - 02/09/1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - USC Dept. R.O. Site Visit, Los Angeles, CA, 1/17/97, 01/17/1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Site Visit, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - IAMA Board Mtg., 12/14/96, College of Physicians, Gross Library (Karen Barton), 12/14/1996 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Carlisle Hospital, 12/12/96, Carlisle, PA, 12/12/1996 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - RSNA, 12/1-6/96, Chicago, IL, 12/01/1996 - 12/06/1996 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Congress on Oncology Meeting, Pisa, Italy, 11/25-27/96 (Prof. Angelo Carpi), 11/25/1996 - 11/27/1996 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Universita Cattolica del Sacro Cuore, Agostino Gemelli, Rome, Italy, 11/19-24/96 (Prof. Numa Cellini), 11/19/1996 - 11/24/1996 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Deutscher Kongress fur Radioonkologie, Strahlenbiologie und Medizinische Physik, Baden-Baden, 11/16-19/96, 11/16/1996 - 11/19/1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - International Symposium, Madrid, Spain, 11/14-15/96 (Dr. Felipe A. Calvo), 11/14/1996 - 11/15/1996 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Malignant Brain Tumors: Future Directions Symposium, 11/9/96, Wyndham Franklin Plaza (Perry Black, MD), 11/09/1996 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - ASTRO Annual Mtg., 11/27-30/96, Los Angeles, CA, 11/27/1996 - 11/30/1996 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - College of Physicians of Phila. New Councillors Orientation Luncheon, 10/22/96, 1 pm, Gross Library, 10/22/1996 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- UP0022 (Box 22)
  - NCI Teleconference Call, 2/28-3/1/95 (Mary Bell, Ph.D.) RE: Jerry R. Williams, Sc.D., 2/28/1995 - 3/1/1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - External Review of Dept. Therapeutic Radiology - Rad. Onc. at U of Minnesota 2/22-23/95 (with Dr. J. Frank Wilson), 02/22/1995 - 02/23/1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Chairs Retreat, Sugarloaf Conference Center, 4/4/95 (Leonard L. Ross, Ph.D.), 04/04/1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Cancer Annual Editorial Advisory Bd. Mtg., Atlanta, GA - Marriott Marquis Hotel, 3/7/95, 03/07/1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Managed Care Mtg., Denver, CO, 3/4-6/95, Oncovail 1995, 03/04/1995 - 06/06/1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Reception at Locks Gallery, Art for BCRI, 3/2/95, 03/02/1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 7th Annual L. Murray Houser, II, MD Memorial Lecture, 4/11/95, Zubrow Auditorium at Pennsylvania Hospital, 04/11/1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - IAMA Spring Board Mtg., 4/22/95, College of Physicians of Phila. (Richard Lippin, MD), 04/22/1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - ARS Scientific Program Committee Conference Call--3/14/94, 5 p.m., 03/14/1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - American Radium Society Annual Mtg., 4/29-5/3/95, Hotel Inter-Continental, Paris, France, 04/29/1995 - 05/03/1995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Univ. of Minnesota CME Course, 5/10-12/95, Minneapolis, MN, 05/10/1995 - 05/12/1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - American Radium Society, Paris, France, 4/29-5/3/95, Hotel Inter-Continental, 04/29/1995 - 05/03/1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - IAMA Meetings: 6/16/95, 7 pm-Merion Cricket Club, 6/17/95, 9:30 am HU 19th Fl. Rm 19-124, 06/16/1995 - 06/17/1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Healthcare Radiation Onc. Q.A. Mtg., 6/12/95, Blue Bell, PA (L. Solin, M.D.), 06/12/1995 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Visiting Prof. at Medical University of South Carolina (MUSC), Charleston, SC, 6/1-2/95 (Andrew Turrisi, M.D.), 06/01/1995 - 06/02/1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - KASRO Mtg., Hershey, PA, 5/19-20/95, 05/19/1995 - 05/20/1995 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - SCAROP - 1995 Training Directors Mtg., 5/18-19/95, Chicago O'Hare Airport, Hyatt Regency (David Hussey, MD), 05/18/1995 - 05/19/1995 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Klinikum Passau, Passau, Germany, 5/15-16/95 (Prof. Dr. Anton Atzinger), 05/15/1995 - 05/16/1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Fifth International Meeting on Progress in Radio-Oncology, 5/11-13/95, 05/11/1995 - 05/13/1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- UP0023 (Box 23)
  - Portrait Presentation of Dr. Frank Miller--GWU, Washington, DC, 4/20/96, Four Seasons Hotel, 04/20/1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - GWU Correspondence, Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - GWU Board of Trustees Retreat, 6/19-20/98, 06/19/1998 - 06/20/1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - GWU Medical Center Committee Mtg., 5/14/98, 3 pm: Ross Holl 713, 2300 Eye St., N.W., Washington, DC, 05/14/1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - GWU Medical Center Committee Mtg., 2/12/98, 3 pm: Ross Hall 713, 2300 Eye St., N.W., 02/12/1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - GWU Bd. of Directors Mtg, 4/30/97, GWU Club, 04/30/1997 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - GWU Campaign Steering Committee, 4/16/97, Washington, DC, 04/16/1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - GWU Reception for New Members, Four Seasons Hotel, Washington, DC, 4/10/97, & Dinner (Bd. Trustees/J. Tractenberg), 04/10/1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - GWU Committee Mtgs. - 2/13/97, GWU Bd. Trustees Mtg - 2/14/97, Washington, DC, 02/13/19 - 02/14/1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - GWU Committee Mtgs. & Board Mtg, 5/15/97, Washington, DC, 05/15/1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - GWU Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner, Renaissance Mayflower Hotel, 5/17/97, Washington, DC, 05/17/1997 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - J. Wallace McMeel, M.D. -- Recipient of the GWU Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award during 5/17-18/97 Commencement Weekend, Washington, DC, 05/17/1997 - 05/18/1997 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - GWU Bd. of Trustees Retreat, 6/20-21/97, Washington, DC, 06/20/1997 - 06/21/1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - GWU- Committee on Development & Alumni Affairs, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - GWU- Committee on Medical Centers, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - John F. Williams, MD, Ed.D., Recommendations, Undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - GWU- Correspondence 1997 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - GWU- New Art Gallery (3/25/02), Luther W. Brady Art Gallery, 03/25/2002 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - GWU Dedication of Weather Vane, Sat., 2/22/2003, in LWB Gallery, 02/22/2003 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- UP0024 (Box 24)
  - Academy of Music Committee Mtg., 2/25/98, Academy House, Suite 320, 02/25/1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia Council Mtg., 4/21/98, 3 p.m., 04/21/1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Human Antibodies & Hybridomas '98 Conference, 4/15-17/98, JW Marriott, Washington, DC, 04/15/1998 - 04/17/1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Lehigh University Fundraising Cocktail Party, 4/8/98, 5 p.m., at 226, 04/08/1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - CANCER Editorial Advisory Board Mtg. 50th Anniv., 4/1/98, 6 p.m., Drake Hotel, New York, NY (Robt. V.P. Hutter, M.D.), 04/01/1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - International Arts-Medicine Association Board Mtg., 3/28/98, 10 am-3 pm, Union League of Phila., 03/28/1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fund Com. Mtg., 3/23-24/98, New Orleans Sheraton Hotel, New Orleans, LA, 03/23/1998 - 03/24/1998 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Villanova University Recent Acquisition Show, 3/22/98, Villanova, PA (Brother Richard Cannuli), 03/22/1998 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - NYC -> Syracuse 3/14/98 - 3/15/98, 03/14/1998 - 3/15/1998 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia Committee on Admissions Mtg. 3/11/98, Gross Library, 03/11/1998 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - NCI Grants Review of MD Anderson Ca Ctr, Houston, TX, 2/22-24/98 (Gail Bryant, MD), 02/22/1998- 02/24/1998 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Society of Gynecologic Oncologists, 2/7-11/98, Orlando, FL, 02/07/1998 - 02/11/1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Academy of Music 141st Anniv. Concert & Ball Wrap Up Mtg., 2/5/98. 10 am. Park Hyatt Phila. at Bellevue, 19th Floor, 02/05/1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Univ. of Maryland Grand Rounds, 1/27/98: Dinner (Carl Mansfield, MD), 1/28/98: Grand Rounds, 01/27/1998 - 01/28/1998 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - CIM Major Gifts Committee Mtg., 1/27/98, 4 pm, Bok Room, 01/27/1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - MCP/Hahnemann School of Medicine Fac. Mtg., 1/21/98, 5 pm, Lecture Hall B, AUH-Hahnemann, 01/21/1998 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - U. of PA. Visiting Professor 1/14/98, Philadelphia, PA (Daniel Canaday, M.D.), 01/14/1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - London, England -- 12/21-27/97, 12/21/1997 - 12/27/1997 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Presbyterian Med. Ctr. of the U of P Health System--Quarterly Med. Staff Mtg., 3/19/97, 6/18/97, 9/17/97, 12/17/97, 03/19/1997 - 12/17/1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - IAMA Board Mtg., College of Physicians, 12/13/1997, 10 a - 4 p (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - College of Physicians Admissions Com. Mtg., Gross Library, 12/10/97, 8:00 am-9:00 am, 12/10/1997 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - PA Acad. of the Fine Arts--Museum of American Art: 10/1/97, Selections Mtg.; 12/7/97, Phila's Choice Exhibition, 10/01/1997 - 12/07/1997 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - RSNA 83rd Scientific Assembly & Annual Mtg., 11/30-12/5/97, McCormick Place, Chicago, IL, 11/30/1997 - 12/05/1997 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Univ. of Leuven, Belgium, 11/15/97 (Prof. Luc Baert/Petrovich/Heilmann), 11/15/1997 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - DEGRO Mtg. (German Soc. for Rad. Onc.), 11/15-18/97, Leipzig, Germany (Prof. Rolf-P. Mueller), 11/15/1997 - 11/18/1997 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - University of Rochester Grand Rounds, 11/5/97, Rochester, NY (Philip Rubin, MD), 11/05/1997 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Revised Documentation Guidelines for Evaluation & Management Svcs. session, 10/29/97, Lecture Hall B, Allegh. Hahnemann, 10/29/1997 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - NRC Mtg., Korman Suites, Phila. PA, 10/28, 29, 30/97 (Andrew Woods, Esq.), 10/28/1997 - 10/30/1997 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia Council Mtg., 10/28/97, 3:30 p.m., Gross Library (Alfred P. Fishman, M.D.), 10/28/1997 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Halifax Medical Center, Daytona Beach, FL, 10/23/97, 10/23/1997 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - BCRI Scientific Program/BCRI Ball, Four Seasons, 9/27/97, 09/27/1997 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Margaret Petrovich, M.D., 9/20/97, Los Angeles, CA, 09/20/1997 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Lehigh University Inaugural Celebration, Opening of Zoellner Arts Center, 9/26-28/97, Bethlehem, PA, 09/26/1997 - 09/28/1997 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Plan A Consulting Telephone Interview, 9/23/97, 2:30 p.m., "Therapeutic Mgmt. of Breast Cancer.", 09/23/1997 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - ACRO Government Day, 9/17/1997, Washington, DC--Capital Hill, 09/17/1997 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - 6th Biennial Mtg. Int'l Gynecologic Ca Soc. (IGCS) Mtg., Fukuoka, Japan, 10/20-24/97, 10/20/1997 - 10/24/1997 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Haverford College, 9/27/97, 2:30 pm, Inauguration of Thomas R. Tritton, Pres. as GWU Board of Trustees Member, 09/27/1997 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - "The Art of Collecting Art," 9/25/97, Cosmopolitan Club (L. Dowling), 09/25/1997 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - RSNA Research and Education Fund Video, Rush-Presby-St. Luke's Hospital, Chicago, IL, 9/24/97, 09/24/1997 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - LaSalle University Art Museum & Gallery, 9/12/97 (Mary Anne Bartley), 09/12/1997 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - ACR Annual Mtg., Atlanta, GA, 9/6-10/97, 09/06/1997 - 09/10/1997 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Daytona Beach, FL 8/28-9/1/97, 08/28/1997 - 09/01/1997 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Mrs. Edith Ferber, 8/15/97, North Egremont, Massachusetts, 08/15/1997 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Northeast Regional Cancer Institute Board Mtg., Scranton, PA 7/22/97, 07/22/1997 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Daytona Beach, Fl--7/3-6/97, 07/03/1997 - 07/06/1997 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- UP0025 (Box 25)
  - GWU Medical Center Committee Mtg., 10/22/98, 3 pm: Ross Hall 713, 2300 Eye St., N.W., Washington, DC, 10/22/1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Cosenza, Italy, Ospedale "Mariano Santo," Opening of Dept. Radiotherapy, Scientific Symposium, 10/17/98 (P. Montemaggi, MD), 10/17/1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NYC Weekend - 10/9-11/98, 10/09/1998 - 10/11/1998 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mallinckrodt Oncology Workshop 10/4-5/98, Hyatt Regency at St. Louis, Union Station, St. Louis, MO, 10/04/1998 - 10/05/1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - ABR, NYC - Plaza Hotel, 10/2/98, 10/02/1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - PharmActinium, Inc. Mtg., 10/1/98 (Maurits W. Geerlings, Jr., M.D.), 10/01/1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Lehigh University Mtg., Four Seasons, Phila., 9/29/98, Gregory C. Farrington, Ph.D., Pres./Jill L. Sherman, VP, Advance., 09/29/1998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - ACR 1998 Annual Meeting, Pittsburgh Hilton and Towers, Pittsburgh, PA, 9/13-16/98, 09/13/1998 - 09/16/1998 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - GW Medical School 50th Reunion Class, 9/10 eve.-9/12 eve./98, Washington, DC (John H. Grossman, III, MD, PhD, MPH), 09/10/1998 - 09/12/1998 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - 1st International Society of Intraoperative Radiation Therapy Mtg., Pamplona, Spain, 9/6-9/98, (Felipe A. Calvo, MD), 09/06/1998 - 09/09/1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - RSNA Research & Educ. Fund Board of Trustees Mtg., 9/1-2/98, Chicago, IL, 09/01/1998 - 09/02/1998 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Lippincott-Rave, Philadelphia, PA, 8/26/98, 4 pm (Christine Rullo/ Karen Phillips), 08/26/1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Santa Fe, NM - Summer 1998, 8/1-15/98, 08/01/1998 - 08/15/1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Aspen, Colorado, 7/24-26/98, 07/24/1998 - 07/26/1998 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - RSNA Research & Edu. Fund Board of Trustees Mtg., 7/21-22/98, Chicago, IL, 07/21/1998 - 07/22/1998 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Seymour H. Levitt, M.D. --70th Birthday, 7/10-12/98, Minneapolis, MN, 07/10/1998 - 07/12/1998 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Innovative Solutions in Healthcare, Inc., Scientific Advisory Board Meeting, 6/27/98, Standard Club, Chicago, IL, 06/27/1998 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - College of Physicians of Phila. Council Meeting, 6/23/98, 3 pm (A. Fishman), 06/23/1998 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - King Faisal Specialist Hosp & Research Centre External Review of Rad. Ther. Svcs, 6/10-16/98, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia (R. Stuart), 06/10/1998 - 06/16/1998 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Riyadh, Saudi Arabia 6/9-17/98, 06/09/1998 - 06/17/1998 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - WCRA Luncheon, 6/6/98, Physick Housem 321 S. 4th St., Phila.., 06/06/1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Univ. of MN - Current Concepts in R.T., 5/20-22/98, Minneapolis, MN (S.H. Levitt), 05/20/1998 - 05/22/1998 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Royal Academy of Medicine of Belgium, 5/16/98, Brussels, Belgium (Prof. J. Henry), 05/16/1998 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Springer Editorial Mtg., 5/11/98, Heidelberg, Germany, 05/11/1998 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - American Radium Society 80th Annual Mtg, Loews Monte Carlo, Monaco--5/2-6/98, 05/02/1998 - 05/06/1998 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - DuPont Hotel Mtg., lobby, 6 p.m. 4/29/98, Dinner - Rm. 208, 7 pm, 04/29/1998 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Northeast Regional Cancer Institute, 4/28/98 Board Mtg., Marian Community Hospital, Carbondale, PA, 04/28/1998 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - 8th Annual Mtg. of ACRO, 4/25-26/98, Park Hyatt Hotel, Washington, DC, 04/25/1998 - 04/26/1998 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- UP0026 (Box 26)
  - Royal Australian & New Zealand College of Radiologists 50th Ann. Scientific Mtg., 10/21-25/99, Sydney, Australia, 10/21/1999 - 10/25/1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Prof. M. Molls' Visit from Technical University of Munich, Munich, Germany to Phila.--Thomas Jefferson Univ., 10/18/99, and Hahnemann Univ. Hosp. 10/19/99, 10/18/1999 - 10/19/1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - ACR 75th Anniversary Mtg., Washington, DC, 9/25-29/99, 09/25/1999 - 09/29/1999 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - College of Physicians of Phila. College Night, Induction of New Fellows-- 9/22/99, 6 pm (LWB speaker- Miyamoto), 09/22/1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fdn. Board of Trustees & Committee Mtgs., 9/15-16/99, 09/15/1999 - 09/16/1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Santa Fe, NM 7/31/99 - 8/14/99, 07/31/1999 - 08/14/1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - University of Stuttgart (Prof. Friedrich H.W. Heuck) 7/22-29/99, 07/22/1999 - 07/29/1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - RSNA R/E Fnd. Mtg. 17 July 1999, regretted, 07/17/1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - International Congress of Radiation (11th), Research, Dublin, Ireland, 7/18-23/99, (M.J. Moriarty, MD), 07/18/1999 - 07/23/1999 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Program in honor of Dr. Seymour Levitt's stepping down as Chairman 6/28-29/99, Minneapolis, MN, 06/28/1999 - 06/29/1999 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - AMA 1999 Distinguished Service Award, 6/20/99, Chicago, IL, 06/20/1999 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - London, England -- 6/10-17/99, 06/10/1999 - 06/17/1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Patrick Cavanaugh, M.D. Memorial, Raleigh, NC 6/1/99, 06/01/1999 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - ABR Oral Examination, Louisville, KY, 5/19-20/99, Orientation: 5/18/99, 05/18/1999 - 05/20/1999 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania Radiological Society Annual Mtg., Hershey, PA, 5/15/99 (Dr. Pyatt, Program Chair), 05/15/1999 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - GWU Bd. of Trustees, Development & Alumni, 5/13/99, 05/13/1999 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - TeleSession on elderly pts. with adv. non-small-cell lung ca with Dr. James R. Rigas, on 5/5/99, 8:30 pm, 05/05/1999 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Dinner Party at 226 -- 5/4/99, 7 p.m., 05/04/1999 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - WEH--Intern't Congress of Ocular Tumors, 5/2-6/99, Philadelphia, PA (J.A. Shields), 05/02/1999 - 05/06/1999 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Colagate University Presidents' Club, Dinner/Tribute to 13th President, Neil R. Grabois, 4/26/1999, Waldorf-Astoria, New York, NY, 04/26/1999 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Post-ARS Seminar, Hiroshima, Japan, 4/24-25/99 (JASTRO Subcommittee) regretted, 04/24/1999 - 04/25/1999 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - GWU 18th Alexander Breslow Memorial Lecture- by Daniel L. Seckinger, M.D., 4/22/99, 04/22/1999 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - South Jersey Medical Ctr. Annual Mtg., Cherry Hill, NJ, Suite 1, 4/19/99 (Gary O. Siemons, MD), 04/19/1999 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - American Radium Society, Maunea Kea Beach Hotel, Big Island of Hawaii-Kona, Hawaii, 4/17-21/99, regretted, 04/17/1999 - 04/21/1999 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fund Trustees Mtg., New Headquarters Bldg., 4/12-13/99, (Dana A. Davis), 04/12/1999 - 04/13/1999 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - West Coast Cancer Foundation Symposium, San Francisco, CA, 4/3-4/99 (John L. Meyer, MD SympDir), 04/03/1999 - 04/04/1999 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Willet, Christopher G., M.D.--Ad Hoc Review Committee for promotion, Harvard Medical School, 3/19/99, 03/19/1999 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Visiting Professor at University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA, 3/10-14/99 (Zbigniew Petrovich, MD), 03/10/1999 - 03/14/1999 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Symposium on New Approaches in Radiation Oncology, Univ. of Munich, 3/4-6/99, Munich, Germany (E. Duhmke, MD), 03/04/1999 - 03/06/1999 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - RTOG Semi-Annual Mtg. Atlanta Hilton & Towers, Atlanta, GA, 1/15-17/99, 01/15/1999 - 01/17/1999 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - New York Medical College: Visiting Prof. & New York Roentgen Society: Speaker 1/11/99, 10 am (Chitti R. Moorthy, MD), 01/11/1999 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Orlando, FL -- 12/28/98 - 1/2/99, 12/28/1998 - 01/02/1999 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Homestead, Hot Springs, VA, 12/23-27/98, 12/23/1998 - 12/27/1998 (Box 26, Folder 33)